Agusti Bau

 $\$ London $\$ agustibau@gmail.com $\$ 1+34699540050 $\$ 5 in/agustibau $\$ 6 www.agustibau.com

SUMMARY

I'm a software engineer with 3 years of experience. I've spent most of my time developing backend systems with java. Nonetheless, I'm always learning, I'm usually tinkering around and I like having some project going on, even if it's only tweaking my Linux machine. Outside of work, I enjoy fixing stuff around the house, and I love balancing on slacklines.

EXPERIENCE

Entrepreneur in residence

Zinc.vc

Sept 2019 - Feb 2020, London

Zinc is a startup incubator with a social focus.

- We explored two ideas in the telemedicine space, developed two prototypes using react and react-native.
- Built multiple relationships with different investors and advisors to start building a business from the ground up.
- Improved my negotiation skills and gained knowledge of how the startup world operates at a higher level.

Software engineer

DataTiger

Oct 2017 - Nov 2018, London

At DataTiger we built a marketing tool, horizontally scalable following a microservices architecture using mainly Java and Python on Docker and AWS.

- I joined at a very early stage, being the 8th hire I developed, designed, and architected key features of the platform.
- I integrated our platform with different systems (email providers, other event providers, ad networks, among others).
- I developed the first parts of the analytics system based on a data lake architecture.
- Architected and developed fail resilient GDPR system, responsible for allowing users to request GDPR deletion of their data.

Junior software engineer

Kina

Jun 2016 - Sep 2017, Barcelona

I joined as an intern during summer 2016, then got hired as a full-time backend developer. We developed a marketing internal system built on Jboss, AWS Redshift and Kafka, using Agile methodologies.

- I implemented end to end rich media notifications across all King games.
- I developed multiple backend features that incorporated into an ETL process.
- Fixed a big amount of bugs

PROJECTS

TubeHabit

- I'm still actively building it, for now, it is a learning project, and I hope I will publish it one day.
- I'm building the whole stack end to end, It's my web dev playground, It allows me to try out new tools and implement features with dubious business value.
- Consists of a web portal that allows us to narrow down property listings by commute time.

Mac Remote

- I created an Android app that allowed to control media playback on OSX devices.
- It got over 200k downloads and about 30 updates over 5 years.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree in computer science

Barcelona School of Informatics • Barcelona • 2018 • 7.3 (out of 10)

SKILLS

Frontend: ES6 javascript, react, react-native, CSS

Backend: Java, Python, Golang, Nodejs